{"data":[{"question":"I wouldn't give a ________ to a young child for his birthday.","a":"flowers","b":"fruit","c":"basket of fruit","d":"money","answer":"3","explain":"\n- A\/an + countable noun and singular noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"Did they ________ to Polihale Beach when they were in Hawaii?","a":"go","b":"went","c":"gone","d":"to go","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The yes\/ no question form in past simple tense: Did + V + Verb + O?","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you think ________ is a good gift?","a":"gloves","b":"money","c":"cookies","d":"chocolates","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Money is uncountable noun- singular verb.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"My grandparents gave me some beautiful ________ when I finished high school.","a":"jewelry","b":"necklace","c":"piece of jewelry","d":"ring","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Jewelry: is uncountable noun.\u00a0\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"A comedy is a movie ________ you laugh.","a":"who makes","b":"who make","c":"that makes","d":"in that makes","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We use that (pronoun) as the subject in the relative clause\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"If you cross your eyes, they ________ that way.","a":"are staying","b":"stayed","c":"wouldn't stay","d":"won't stay","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Condition type I: If + simple present, simple future tense\/simple present tense.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"Andrew is very good ________ jokes.","a":"for telling","b":"in telling","c":"at telling","d":"about telling","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To be good at sth\/doing sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"We plan to investigate the possibility ________ spending a week at the seashore.","a":"in","b":"of","c":"on","d":"for","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Possibility of doing sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"What will happen if you ________ to a lot of loud music?","a":"have listened","b":"are listening","c":"listen","d":"listened","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Condition type I: If + simple present, simple future tense\/simple present tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"Huge areas have been ________ because of the nuclear accident.","a":"evacuated","b":"transmitted","c":"restrained","d":"disturbed","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Evacuate: to send people away from a dangerous place to a safe place.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"}]}